Hello and welcome to The Machine Learning engineer nano-degree program, I'm Luis Serrano.
大家好 欢迎学习机器学习纳米学位 我是 Luis Serrano
I'm Arpen Chakraborty.
我是 Arpan Chakraborty
And we are the program's lead instructors.
我们是该课程的讲师
Machine learning is becoming indispensable to companies across
机器学习对于各行各业来说
all industries and new applications are being devised every day.
都成为了必不可少的技术 每天都会有新的应用层出不穷
You may have heard about how Netflix recommends movies based on your tastes or how
你可能听说过 Netflix 根据你的个人喜欢推荐电影
Facebook is using machine learning to automatically tag faces and pictures.
Facebook 使用机器学习自动为头像和照片添加标签
But machine learning is not just relevant in consumer applications,
但是机器学习不仅仅会出现在面向消费者的应用中
it's also changing how large enterprises operate.
而且也在逐渐改变大型企业的运营方式
Google is using predictive modeling to reduce their data center
Google 使用预测性建模
operating costs and PayPal is using
来降低数据中心的运营成本
deep neural networks to detect fraudulent transactions.
PayPal 使用深度神经网络来监测欺诈性交易
Accordingly, machine learning engineers are consistently some of the most in demand jobs,
自然地 机器学习工程师成为最紧缺最为行业所青睐的职位
particularly in the tech world.
尤其是在技术领域 甚是火爆
The goal of this program is to help you develop all the skills you need
本课程的目标是帮助你掌握
to start or advance your career as a machine learning engineer.
早这一领域职业发展所需的所有技能 以成为一名机器学习工程师
Not only will you learn the concepts of machine learning in detail,
你不仅将详细了解机器学习的基础概念
but you'll also graduate with a portfolio of real world projects,
而且在毕业后将拥有用实战项目组成的作品集
where you'll use machine learning algorithms to analyze real data.
你将在这些项目中利用机器学习算法分析实际数据
Udacity's network of subject matter experts will review your projects and
优达学城的多位专家将审阅你的项目
give you invaluable feedback to support mastery of these new skill sets.
向你提供详细的个性化反馈 帮助你掌握这些新的技能
This program has been built for students with some math and coding knowledge.
该课程需要你具有一定的数学和编程知识
If you're comfortable with derivative and matrices and you can do some coding in Python,
如果你熟悉导数和矩阵 并且可以用 Python Java C
Java, C, or any language, you're ready to start.
或任何其他语言编程 那么你可以开始学习这门课程了
In this program, you'll learn what a machine learning model
在此课程中 你将了解什么是机器学习模型
is and what are the main algorithms of supervised and unsupervised learning.
以及有哪些主要监督学习算法和非监督学习算法
You'll learn how to train and test algorithms and how to evaluate and validate them.
你将学习如何训练和测试算法 以及如何评估和验证这些算法
You'll get a solid knowledge of the main algorithms of
你将掌握监督式机器学习算法的相关知识
supervised machine learning including linear logistic regression,
包括线性逻辑回归
decision trees, support vector machines and neural networks.
决策树 支持向量机和神经网络
Also you'll learn the main algorithms of
此外 你还将学习非监督学习的主要算法
unsupervised learning including clustering and dimensionality reduction.
包括聚类和降维
And then, we'll dig deep into two topics,
然后 我们将深入讲解以下两个概念
deep learning and reinforcement learning.
深度学习和强化学习
In deep learning, you'll learn deep neural networks and
在深度学习部分 你将学习深度神经网络
convolutional neural networks used primarily for image recognition.
和卷积神经网络 这些网络主要用于识别图片
Then, you'll learn reinforcement learning,
然后 你将学习强化学习
where you will train agents to carry out optimal actions starting
你将训练智能体执行最优动作
with mark-off decision processes and classic reinforcement learning algorithms,
从标记决策流程开始 到经典强化学习算法流程
progressing to cutting edge deep reinforcement learning.
并掌握前沿性深度强化学习的算法
And at the end, you will be able to apply all you've learned to
最后 你将能够在毕业实战项目中
a problem and data set of your choice in your capstone project.
运用所学的知识解决你所选的问题和数据集
Now, don't worry if that sounds daunting,
如果听起来有点困难 别担心
you'll get feedback from our network of expert reviewers along
我们的多位专业审阅专家将一直为你提供指导
the way to guide you and help you make your capstone project a reality.
帮助你成功完成毕业项目
When you complete this program you'll graduate ready to get a job as
当你学完该课程后 你将能够成功应聘
a machine learning engineer or to
机器学习工程师职位
continue your journey in the world of machine learning, cheers.
或在机器学习领域继续发展 加油
Cheers.
加油